ELLEN GAULT

IT GRADUATE ♥ LIVERPOOL, L1, UNITED KINGDOM **♦** 07526633793

• DETAILS •

Liverpool, L1 United Kingdom 07526633793 ellen.gault7@yahoo.com

• LINKS •

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ellen-gault-3912421b1/

https://github.com/ellengault/

o SKILLS o

Leadership

Effective Time Management

Computer Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team

Customer Service

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Communication Skills

Microsoft Office

HOBBIES

Keeping in shape is important for me, as this improves all aspects of my life. I also enjoy cooking and trying new recipes, especially with family and friends.

♣ PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic and highly adaptive individual with a desire for new challenges and the first step of my career. A combination of previous experience, education and hobbies have strengthened my abilities, in the particular communication, teamwork, preparation and managerial skills. Always pushing myself to learn more whether it's ICT knowledge, literature, or ways to benefit my overall health - the idea for continuous learning is a key competency of mine. Working hard and performing at a level that I can be proud of and asserting myself as a key asset to a team is extremely important to me. My educational and employment achievements in particular my degree has only increased my passion for ICT and IT operations, making myself highly motivated and would love to enhance my skill set within this realm.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

NHS Test and Trace Assistant at Compass then Sodexo, Liverpool

October 2020 — Present

This role is heavily based on health and safety measures as it is a high risk. It is a rewarding job that has taught me excellent time management skills.

My role involves working with customers of all ages and abilities, guiding them through the testing process, being empathetic, comforting and professional, as well as informing them of government guidelines and ensuring social distancing is maintained. Cleaning and registration are also required within this role.

Responsibilities include:

- · Being informative and helpful during the test process
- · Ensuring the sanitising of all customer-facing areas
- · Instructing customers on the registration process
- •The ability to follow strict processes, guidelines and procedures.

Throughout my role here it was and is extremely important to be vigilant and maintain social distancing at all times. It was very important to be a team player and help out teammates with any problems which they encountered or were unsure of, have an enthusiastic and positive attitude towards work and subjects, fully flexible and was able to come in last minute and travel to many different locations within and outside of Merseyside. It was important that I had excellent customer service skills and went above and beyond for both my work colleagues and those who came for a test whilst remaining calm under pressure during the busy mass testing and for anyone who had any issues, problems or complaints. I also took on supervisorial roles during my time at Compass providing support for the manager whilst they were limited, ensuring that the van was set up correctly, the team members had everything required for a successful and positive day whilst respecting and treating everyone equally.

Customer Assistant at Cathcart's Centra, Kilrea

April 2018 — September 2020

This role included providing excellent customer service skills along with the organisation of stock onto shelves, price reductions and stock ordering.

Responsibilities include:

- · Effectively carrying out cash and card payments as well as refunds and exchanges.
- \cdot Efficiently processing lottery terminal transactions, scratch card sales along to bacco products.

- · Packing bakery products along with delivery.
- · Floating tills
- Delivering a high level of customer service through working as a team and effectively engaging with the public.

I also had the responsibility of opening the shop myself at 7 am and then closing the shop myself at 10 pm as I was reliable and trustworthy with my own set of keys. In addition to this, I took on the role within the Deli located in the shop, cooking and prepping breakfasts, lunches and prepacked lunch meals for on the go. Ensuring there was a high standard of food hygiene throughout I developed the trust and responsibility to operate in line with the Food Safety regulations completing any appropriate paperwork daily and following correct protocols. During my studies in school, I obtained the Level 2 Food Hygiene Certificate which allowed me to complete said tasks successfully.

Manager at Brae Mar Guest House, Portrush

March 2017 — September 2020

Brae-Mar B&B welcomes and provides tourists from all across the world a friendly, comfortable and the upmost cleanliness and hygienic stay. The tasks which I was involved in while working at Brae-Mar were as follows:

- The preparation of setting up the dining room and kitchen for cooking and servings of breakfast, ensuring there is a high level of health and safety measures taken place at every stage.
- Connecting with the guests to ensure there was a relationship created which gave outstanding customer service.
- The busy environment entailed a high level of organisation skills and multitasking when cooking the breakfast, connecting with the guests and prioritising different tasks. It allowed me to develop skills to stay calm in pressured situations or resolve a problem the guests may have successfully and professionally.
- After the breakfasts were completed I had the responsibility to take large payments for their stays and then carried out housekeeping duties within the rooms, ensuring they were completed to a high cleanliness standard.
- I had the responsibility of being the key holder for the B&B, and demonstrating managerial and team-leading roles by ensuring there were high levels of communication between myself and another colleague and the tasks was prioritised correctly.

EDUCATION

GCSE qualifications, Coleraine Grammar School, Coleraine

August 2010 — June 2017

During my time at this school, I obtained 10 GCSES ranging from grades A-C including both Maths, English and ICT.

A Level, Grammar School, Coleraine

August 2015 — August 2017

During my time here I studied and obtained the following; ICT - B, Health and Social Care - C and Home Economics - D.

Information Technology, Media and Communication (BA) Hons, Liverpool Hope University, Liverpool

September 2017 — June 2020

During my 3 years of study at this university, began and developed my love and interests in Information Technology and the use of digital media. Obtaining a Second Division Upper-Class Honours, examples of the recent modules completed include Internet of Things, Game Development with Lua, Digital Media Concepts and my dissertation 'The Investigation Of Users' Perception Of Computer Viruses and Dangers of Public Wi-Fi Particularly, For Social Media Use and Whether Obsession Of Platforms Causes Ignorance

To Potential Malicious Scams And Links'. The following were also learnt and used throughout my studies-

Programming: HTML, Java, JavaScript, PHP, CSS, Lua, Phython

Databases: MySQL, SQL server,

Miscellaneous: Windows Server 2019, Microsoft Office (Access, Excel, Powerpoint Word), Adobe Programs (InDesign, PhotoShop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro)

■ REFERENCES

Neil Buckley from Hope University

bucklen@hope.ac.uk

Angela Cathcart from Centra Kilrea

07594 680227

Brian Bell from Brae-Mar B&B

07801 480361

COURSES

Level 2 Health and Safety, Grammar School

September 2015 — September 2015